https://www.weathersavvy.com/pages/privacy-policy

Cart
"Close Cart"
PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy sets out how we, collect, store and use information about you when you use or interact with our website, weathersavvy.com (our website) and where we otherwise obtain or collect information about you. This Privacy Policy is effective from May 1, 2018.
Our Promise to YouOur privacy policy is our commitment to treat the information you provide with care to protect your personal information. We keep our privacy updated for your needs, new technologies and changing best business practice.
We strive for excellence in both the quality of our products and the services we provide and in the safeguarding of your personal information.
What Does This Policy Cover?
Our privacy policy covers personal information that we collect, use, and protect when you visit our site and purchase products and services.
What Types of Information Do We Collect?There are two basic types of information collected when you visit any website:
1. Disclosed information.2. Browsing information.
Disclosed InformationYou choose to provide this information because it is needed to let you buy products and services or to receive direct emails from us.
1. Financial and PersonalWhen you purchase from one of our partners or us, you provide the following information:
· Your name.· Your address or a mailing address.· Email address· Phone numbers – home, business, or mobile· Relevant personal information· Credit card number
As part of the purchase process, you authorize payment and allow us to seek information from credit agencies. This information is routine in online transactions.
2. Email AddressYou may talk to us by email, telephone and letter. We protect all forms of communication with us. We may retain the contents of the emails exchanged between us for our files. We safeguard all forms of communication with us as part of our commitment to client privacy.
Browsing InformationWe maintain a commercial Web site and employ standard technologies – cookies and Web server logs. These tools collect this type of information:
· Date and time of visit.· The pages you view.· The time spent on our Web pages.· The Websites you visit immediately before and after your visit to us.
This bulk information (100 visits at 10.00 am) is not linked to an individual.
1. Cookies
Cookies allow a Web server to recognize your computer when you come back to our Web site. The cookie is the name given to the small bit of data that your web browser stores on your computer. It tags what web pages you visit so when you return; you find the information or page quickly. The idea is to provide you with a better online experience.
2. Web Server LogsThese count the number of people visiting and how many we can accommodate.
These website tools do not collect email addresses or any personal information. They do allow us to send out targeted online banner advertising.
What Do We Do with the Information?
Disclosed InformationPrincipally we use the information to run our business.
· We sell goods and services and use this information to get paid and send you the product.· We tell you about other products that might benefit you.· We keep you in the loop with information about changes to our Web pages, new products, and special offers.
We aim to provide you with information that is relevant and interesting to you, and we don’t bother you too frequently. You can unsubscribe from communications at any time and once a year we remind you that you don’t have to receive information from us if you don’t find it helpful.
The list used to send out information is kept separate from personal account information. We apply high standards to our list management and safeguard your sensitive data.
We value the ability to communicate directly with our clients, and we are careful not to abuse the privilege.
Browser Information
We use this anonymous information to provide us with valuable insights into our customers' needs. This business information allows us to design a website that is friendly and easy to use. We are committed to continual improvement and this information helps us build a better, more responsive service through our website.
Sharing Information
We may share limited information with affiliates and strategic partners.
Affiliates are other companies whose products and services may benefit our customers. We allow them to advertise their offers on our Web site. We believe that they maintain the same high standards as us, but we cannot guarantee or vouch for their policies and procedures.
Links to and from other websites are signposting information for customers, and we do not vouch for other websites' policies and procedures.
We may have strategic arrangements for marketing or some other activity with a third party. We may share bulk anonymous information with them about our customers. We retain ownership of the data.
We never disclose your personal information, financial details, or contact details with outside organizations. The exception being legal disclosure for the protection of our legal rights or a lawful request by a relevant authority.
Information Security
We use encryption and security software to protect your personal information. We use a 128-bit (or more) secure socket layer encryption (SSL) for pages collecting personal sensitive information. The data is encrypted when you enter it and then decoded when it reaches our website. This process protects against:
· Someone else gaining access to your personal information· Accidental or deliberate disclosure of information.· Accidental loss, destruction or alteration of the information you send.
All personal information is given to enable the customer to buy goods and services and cannot be shared, saved, disclosed, or used by a third party without written authorization.
We regularly check our policies and procedures to ensure that we are meeting our high corporate standards for keeping your information safe and private.
Our employees receive regular training in our policies, standards, and values. Only authorized employees can access your information and for specific business purposes.
Controlling Your Information*You can stop receiving information from us by emailing service@weathersavvy.com*You can check that the information held about you is correct by emailing service@weathersavvy.com and requesting a copy of the details held about you on our database.
Added to cart!
Yuwell. You, me love life 22 Years!
